export const quizQuestions_4 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the main purpose of using React Router?',
      choices: ['For state management', 'For data binding', 'For navigation and routing', 'For handling forms'],
      correctAnswer: 'For navigation and routing',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a Fragment in React?',
      choices: ['A tool for managing state', 'A component for grouping multiple elements', 'A method for fetching data', 'A function for handling events'],
      correctAnswer: 'A component for grouping multiple elements',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, what can be used to pass data from a parent to a deeply nested child component directly?',
      choices: ['Props', 'State', 'Context', 'Reducers'],
      correctAnswer: 'Context',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the term "Reconciliation" refer to in React?',
      choices: ['Synchronizing state and props', 'The process by which React updates the DOM', 'Combining multiple reducers', 'Resolving conflicts in version control'],
      correctAnswer: 'The process by which React updates the DOM',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the use of the useRef hook in React?',
      choices: ['To create a reference to a DOM element', 'To store the previous state', 'To manage form inputs', 'To make API calls'],
      correctAnswer: 'To create a reference to a DOM element',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method in a React class component is called right before a component is removed from the DOM?',
      choices: ['componentDidUnmount', 'componentWillUnmount', 'componentWillMount', 'componentDidMount'],
      correctAnswer: 'componentWillUnmount',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the primary role of the useState hook in functional components?',
      choices: ['To manage component lifecycle', 'To manipulate the DOM', 'To add local state to the component', 'To fetch data from an API'],
      correctAnswer: 'To add local state to the component',
    },
    {
      question: 'How is data flow in React components typically described?',
      choices: ['Two-way data binding', 'Multi-directional data flow', 'Unidirectional data flow', 'Bidirectional data flow'],
      correctAnswer: 'Unidirectional data flow',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the common use case for the useReducer hook in React?',
      choices: ['To handle simple state logic', 'For managing global state', 'To handle complex state logic involving multiple sub-values', 'For data fetching'],
      correctAnswer: 'To handle complex state logic involving multiple sub-values',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, what is the purpose of the StrictMode component?',
      choices: ['To enforce strict coding conventions', 'To identify potential problems in an application', 'To enhance security measures', 'To restrict component usage'],
      correctAnswer: 'To identify potential problems in an application',
    }
  ]
};
